Guide to the Liederkranz Collection ca. 1847-1987 MSS.130
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Printed Sheet Music Collection
  - Composer: Fuhrich, Carl Title: Dem Unendlichen Uniform Title: Unendlichen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 14323 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 101, Folder 1322)
  - Composer: Fuhrich, Carl Title: Ralf Ringelhaar Uniform Title: Ralf Ringelhaar Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 6464, undated (Box 124, Folder 1805)
  - Composer: Fuhrich, Carl Title: Ralf Ringelhaar Uniform Title: Ralf Ringelhaar Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F.E.C.L.6465, undated (Box 158, Folder 2513)
  - Composer: Fuhrich, Carl Title: Ralf Ringelhaar Uniform Title: Ralf Ringelhaar Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F.E.C.L.6513, undated (Box 158, Folder 2512)
  - Composer: Gabriel-Marie Title: La Cinquantaine Uniform Title: Cinquantaine Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 10744, undated (Box 105, Folder 1474)
  - Composer: Gabriel-Marie Title: Serenade Badine Uniform Title: Serenade Badine Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 3472-9, undated (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Comala Uniform Title: Comala Plate Number: 10,863, undated (Box 133, Folder 1890)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Comala Uniform Title: Comala Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 7543, undated (Box 133, Folder 1889)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Die Kreuzfahrer Uniform Title: Kreuzfahrer Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 11094, undated (Box 139, Folder 1939)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Die Kreuzfahrer Uniform Title: Kreuzfahrer Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 11109, undated (Box 140, Folder 1962)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Die Kreuzfahrer Uniform Title: Kreuzfahrer Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 11112, undated (Box 140, Folder 1961)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Die Kreuzfahrer Uniform Title: Kreuzfahrer Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 11293, undated (Box 163, Folder 2720)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Erlkonigs Tochter. Ballade Uniform Title: Erlkonigs Tochter Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 2075, undated (Box 115, Folder 1634)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Erlkonigs Tochter Uniform Title: Erlkonigs Tochter Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 2074, undated (Box 134, Folder 1892)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Erlkonigs Tochter Uniform Title: Erlkonigs Tochter Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 2076, undated (Box 134, Folder 1891)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Erlkonigs Tochter Uniform Title: Erlkonigs Tochter Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 2858, undated (Box 134, Folder 1893)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Fruhlings-Botschaft Uniform Title: Fruhlings-Botschaft Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 9810, undated (Box 160, Folder 2628)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Fruhlings-Botschaft Uniform Title: Fruhlings-Botschaft Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 9811, undated (Box 160, Folder 2627)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Gondelfahrt Uniform Title: Gondelfahrt Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholf Senff Plate Number: 78,424, undated (Box 157, Folder 2483)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Holbegian. Suite fur Orchester Uniform Title: Holberg suite, op. 61 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): V. Durdilly, Paris (Breitkopf & Härtel [printer]) Plate Number: 17130/32, undated, undated (Box 18, Folder 205)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Holbergiana. Suite fur Orchester Uniform Title: Holberg suite, op. 61 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 17130, undated (Box 18, Folder 204)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Kalanus Uniform Title: Kalanus Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 12164, undated (Box 112, Folder 1601)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Kalanus Uniform Title: Kalanus Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 12199, undated (Box 111, Folder 1599)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Kalanus Uniform Title: Kalanus Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 12223, undated (Box 111, Folder 1600)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Kalanus Uniform Title: Kalanus Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 12363, undated (Box 165, Folder 2792)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Nachklange von Ossian, op. 1 Uniform Title: Nachklange von Ossian. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.181., undated (Box 18, Folder 207)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Nachklange von Ossian. Konzert-Ouverture fur Orchester, op. 1 Uniform Title: Nachklange von Ossian. Ouverture. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Part.B.193., undated (Box 18, Folder 206)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Reiters Morgenlied Uniform Title: Reiters Morgenlied Plate Number: 1595, undated (Box 169, Folder 2979)
  - Composer: Gageur, Eugen Title: Die Krone im Rhein Uniform Title: Krone im Rhein Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: G.H.1742 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 149, Folder 2154)
  - Composer: Galbraith, J. Lamont Title: Give a Man a Horse He Can Ride Uniform Title: Give a Man a Horse He Can Ride Publisher information: Boston: Oliver Ditson Company Plate Number: 75760-9, undated (Box 162, Folder 2686)
  - Composer: Gall, Jan, arr. Title: Marietta Uniform Title: Marietta Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 4463 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 166, Folder 2859)
  - Composer: Gall, Jan Title: Frau Einzig Uniform Title: Frau Einzig Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F.E.C.L. 4061 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 158, Folder 2522)
  - Composer: Gall, Jan Title: Madchen mit dem rothen Mundchen Uniform Title: Madchen mit dem rothen Mundchen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 3865 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 167, Folder 2892)
  - Composer: Gall, Jan Title: Maiden with the lips so rosy Uniform Title: Madchen mit dem rothen Mundchen Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 4755, undated (Box 167, Folder 2893)
  - Composer: Gall, Jan Title: Maritetta Uniform Title: Marietta Publisher information: New York: Luckhardt & Belder Plate Number: 178, undated (Box 172, Folder 3094)
  - Composer: Gambke, Fritz Title: Das Katzchen Uniform Title: Katzchen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Part.B. 1979., undated (Box 149, Folder 2156)
  - Composer: Gamse, Albert, arr. Title: Havah Nagilah Uniform Title: Havah Nagilah Publisher information: New York: Larrabee Publications, undated (Box 175, Folder 3301)
  - Composer: Gartner, John B. Title: Das Lied vom schlimmen Matrosen Uniform Title: Lied vom schlimmen Matrosen; arr., undated (Box 80, Folder 1028)
  - Composer: Gartner, John B. Title: Matrosenlied Uniform Title: Matrosenlied; arr. Publisher information: New York: Quartet Publishing House, undated (Box 167, Folder 2865)
  - Composer: Gasteiner, Robert Title: Luarin Uniform Title: Luarin Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 6473 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 165, Folder 2804)
  - Composer: Gay, Noel Title: There's Something about a Soldier Uniform Title: Soldiers of the King. There's Something about a Soldier Publisher information: New York: Mills Music Inc. Music Publishers, undated (Box 159, Folder 2555)
  - Composer: Geehl, Henry Ernest Title: Dawn. A Prelude Uniform Title: Dawn. A Prelude; arr. Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Gould & Bolttler Plate Number: G & B. 1656., undated (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Composer: Geibel, Adam Title: Annie Laurie Uniform Title: Annie Laurie Publisher information: Boston: Oliver Ditson Company Plate Number: F. A. N. & Co. 3817.6, undated (Box 147, Folder 2098)
  - Composer: Genaro, Pat, and Sunny Skylar Title: You're Breaking My Heart Uniform Title: You're Breaking My Heart Publisher information: New York: Algonquin Music Inc., undated (Box 158, Folder 2533)
  - Composer: Genee, Richard Title: Italienischer Salat Uniform Title: Italienischer Salat Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 2541, undated (Box 162, Folder 2692)
  - Composer: Genee, Richard Title: Reise um die Erde in 12 Minuten Uniform Title: Reise um die Erder in 12 Minuten Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Friedrich Schreiber (A. Eckel, Vienna [printer]) Plate Number: F. S.23876. Engraver: Eberle & Schipek, undated (Box 124, Folder 1797)
  - Composer: Gericke, Wilhelm Title: O welt du bist so wunderschon! Uniform Title: O welt du bist so wunderschon! Plate Number: L. & S. 131, undated (Box 168, Folder 2906)
  - Composer: German folksong Title: Christmas Night Uniform Title: Weihnacht; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 12636, undated (Box 148, Folder 2130)
  - Composer: German, Edward, Sir Title: Gipsy Suite. Four Characteristic Dances Uniform Title: Gipsy Suite. Four Characteristic Dances Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Novello and Company Plate Number: 9933, undated (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Composer: German, Edward, Sir Title: Suite Uniform Title: Suite; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 22917, undated (Box 19, Folder 212)
  - Composer: Gernsheim, Friedrich Title: Das Grab im Busento Uniform Title: Grab im Busento Plate Number: F. L. 138, undated (Box 147, Folder 2090)
  - Composer: Gernsheim, Friedrich Title: Odin's Meeresritt Uniform Title: Odin's Meeresritt Publisher information: New York: Edward Schuberth & Co., undated (Box 112, Folder 1608)
  - Composer: Gernsheim, Friedrich Title: Salamis. Siegesgesang der Griechen Uniform Title: Salamis. Siegesgesang der Griechen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 499, undated (Box 138, Folder 1930)
  - Composer: Gernsheim, Friedrich Title: Salamis. Siegesgesang der Griechen Uniform Title: Salamis. Siegesgesang der Griechen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann Plate Number: 503, undated (Box 138, Folder 1929)
  - Composer: Gersbach, Jos. Title: Voglein, Blumlein und Bachlein Uniform Title: Voglein, Blumlein und Bachlein, undated (Box 115, Folder 1643)
  - Composer: Gevaert, François-Auguste Title: The Emigrants Uniform Title: Auswanderer Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 3602, undated (Box 155, Folder 2409)
  - Composer: Giese, Theodor Title: Blümlein vergiss mein nicht (Flowret Forget-me-not). Gavotte Uniform Title: Blümlein vergiss mein nicht Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 15948, undated (Box 105, Folder 1471)
  - Composer: Gilbert, Jean Title: All for the Girlies Uniform Title: Autoliebchen. Das Haben die Madchen so gerne, undated (Box 145, Folder 2025)
  - Composer: Gillet, E. Title: Bonheur Perdu (Lost Happiness) Uniform Title: Bonheur Perdu; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 3627-18, undated (Box 18, Folder 208)
  - Composer: Gillet, Ernest Title: Au Moulin (In der Muhle) Uniform Title: Au Moulin; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 2314-27, undated (Box 96, Folder 1201)
  - Composer: Gillet, Ernest Title: Babillage (Plauderei) Uniform Title: Babillage; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 2314-27, undated (Box 96, Folder 1200)
  - Composer: Gillet, Ernest Title: Douce Caresse (Zartliche Umarmung) Uniform Title: Douce caresse Publisher information: Nice (France): Paul Decourcelle (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: P. D. 251, undated (Box 98, Folder 1238)
  - Composer: Gillet, Ernest Title: Loin du bal. Waltz Movement Uniform Title: Loin du bal; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 1894-11, undated (Box 104, Folder 1404)
  - Composer: Ginkel, Henry, and Al Havranek, arr. Title: Alter Sang, Neuer Klang Uniform Title: Alter Snag, Neuer Klang Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer, undated (Box 109, Folder 1557)
  - Composer: Girschner, C. F. J. Title: Hute dich! Uniform Title: Hute dich! Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Carl Simon, Musikverlag Plate Number: C. S. 1946, undated (Box 162, Folder 2671)
  - Composer: Girschner, C. F. J. Title: Hute dich! Uniform Title: Hute dich! Publisher information: Bremen (Germany): A. E. Fischer Plate Number: 2537, undated (Box 162, Folder 2672)
  - Composer: Girschner, C. F. J. Title: Hute dich! Uniform Title: Hute dich! Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Ernst Eulenberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: E. E. 823 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 162, Folder 2669)
  - Composer: Girschner, C. F. J. Title: Hute dich! Uniform Title: Hute dich! Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Ernst Eulenberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: E. E. 824 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 162, Folder 2670)
  - Composer: Girschner, C. F. J. Title: Hute dich! Uniform Title: Hute dich! Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug & Co. Plate Number: G. H. 3045., undated (Box 162, Folder 2673)
  - Composer: Girschner, C. F. J. Title: Hute dich! Uniform Title: Hute dich! Publisher information: Offenbach a/M (Germany): Johann Andre Plate Number: 7591, undated (Box 162, Folder 2674)
  - Composer: Glazunov, Aleksandr Konstantinovich Title: Marche, op. 76 Uniform Title: Marche, op. 76 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): M. P. Belaieff Plate Number: 2372, undated (Box 19, Folder 213)
  - Composer: Glazunov, Aleksandr Konstantinovich Title: Novelette, op. 22, no. 2 Uniform Title: Novelette, op. 22, no. 2; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 22370-41, undated (Box 19, Folder 214)
  - Composer: Glazunov, Aleksandr Konstantinovich Title: Valse de Concert pour Grand Orchestre, op. 47 Uniform Title: Valse de Concert pour Grand Orchestre, op. 47 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): M. P. Belaieff Plate Number: 918 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 19, Folder 215)
  - Composer: Glazunov, Aleksandr Konstantinovich Title: Valse de Concert, op. 47 Uniform Title: Valse de Concert, op. 47 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): M. P. Belaieff Plate Number: 919, undated (Box 19, Folder 216)
  - Composer: Glessmer, Felix Title: Schon bluh'n die Heckenrosen Uniform Title: Schon bluh'n die Heckenrosen, undated (Box 172, Folder 3086)
  - Composer: Glinka, Mikhail Ivanovich Title: Kamarinskaia Uniform Title: Kamarinskaia Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): M. P. Belaiff Plate Number: 3011 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 19, Folder 217)
  - Composer: Glinka, Mikhail Ivanovich Title: Rouslane et Ludmila. Ouverture Uniform Title: Ruslan I Liudmila. Ouverture Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne Plate Number: 15899., undated (Box 19, Folder 218)
  - Composer: Gluck, Christoph Willibald Title: Iphigenia in Aulis. Ouverture Uniform Title: Iphigenie en Aulide. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.182., undated (Box 20, Folder 225)
  - Composer: Gluck, Christoph Willibald Title: Iphigenia in Aulis. Ouverture Uniform Title: Iphigenie en Aulide. Ouverture Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: C. 39382., undated (Box 20, Folder 226)
  - Composer: Glueck, F. Title: Untreue Uniform Title: Untreue Plate Number: 7162, undated (Box 173, Folder 3151)
  - Composer: Glueck, F. Title: Untreue Uniform Title: Untreue Plate Number: 7163, undated (Box 127, Folder 1840)
  - Composer: Glueck, Fr., arr. Title: Klage Uniform Title: Klage; arr. Publisher information: New York: F. A. Rockar Plate Number: F. A. R. 701-4, undated (Box 127, Folder 1839)
  - Composer: Gobbaerts, Jean-Louis Title: Les Puritains. Opera de Bellini. Fantaisie Brillante Uniform Title: Puritains. Fantaisie brillante Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: S. F. 2751, undated (Box 104, Folder 1419)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Louis Paul Title: Six Duets for 2 violins with piano accompaniment Uniform Title: Duettini, 2 violins & piano, op. 18 Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 6905, undated (Box 99, Folder 1276)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: 2me. Mazurk Uniform Title: Mazurka, piano, no. 2 Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 4759, undated (Box 105, Folder 1439)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: Adagio Pathetique, op. 128, no. 3 Uniform Title: Adagio Pathetique, op. 128, no. 3; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 22201, undated (Box 20, Folder 227)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: Berceuse from Jocelyn Uniform Title: Jocelyn. Berceuse; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 4689-36, undated (Box 20, Folder 228)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: Canzonetta, op. 35, no. 3 Uniform Title: Canzonetta, op. 35, no. 3; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 23003, undated (Box 19, Folder 220)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: Deauxieme Mazurk, op. 54 Uniform Title: Deauxieme Mazurk, op. 54 Publisher information: Boston: White-Smith Music Publishing Co. Plate Number: 6942-8, undated (Box 100, Folder 1284)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: Jocelyn. Act 2. Prelude Uniform Title: Jocelyn. Act 2. Prelude Publisher information: Paris (France) (E. Dupre, Paris [printer]) Plate Number: A.C. 7124, undated (Box 20, Folder 231)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: Jocelyn. Act 2 Uniform Title: Jocelyn. Act 2 Publisher information: Paris (France) Plate Number: A.C. 7909, undated (Box 20, Folder 230)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: Jocelyn. Gavotte Uniform Title: Jocelyn. Gavotte Publisher information: Paris (France): Choudens Fils Plate Number: A.C. 8119, undated (Box 20, Folder 229)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: Scenes Poetiques Uniform Title: Scenes Poetiques; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 22232, undated (Box 19, Folder 219)
  - Composer: Goebel, Friedel Title: Du bist verkehrt verheirat Uniform Title: Du bist verkehrt verheirat Publisher information: Wuppertal-Langerfeld (Germany): Hermann Goebel, undated (Box 145, Folder 2054)
  - Composer: Goetz, Hermann Title: Es liegt so abendstill der See Uniform Title: Es liegt so abendstill der See (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 7718, undated (Box 154, Folder 2390)
  - Composer: Goetz, Hermann Title: Es liegt so abendstill der See Uniform Title: Es liegt so abendstill der See Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 7719 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 131, Folder 1882)
  - Composer: Goetz, Hermann Title: Es liegt so abendstill der See Uniform Title: Es liegt so abendstill der See Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 7721 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 131, Folder 1883)
  - Composer: Goldmark, Carl Title: Bridal Song and Serenade from Rural Wedding Symphony Uniform Title: Landliche Hochzeit. Brautlied and Serenade; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 6369-45, undated (Box 19, Folder 221)
  - Composer: Goldmark, Carl Title: Einzugsmarsch der Konigin von Saba Uniform Title: Konigin von Saba. Einzugsmarsch Publisher information: Hamburg (Germany): Hugo Pohle (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 344. H.P. 342. Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 118, Folder 1690)
  - Composer: Goldmark, Carl Title: Einzugsmarsch der Konigin von Saba Uniform Title: Konigin von Saba. Einzugsmarsch Publisher information: Hamburg (Germany): Hugo Pohle (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: H. P. 377 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 160, Folder 2623)
  - Composer: Goldmark, Carl Title: Einzugsmarsch der Konigin von Saba Uniform Title: Konigin von Saba. Einzugsmarsch Publisher information: Hamburg (Germany): Hugo Pohle (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: H.P.345 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 118, Folder 1691)
  - Composer: Goldmark, Carl Title: Festlicher Einzugs-Marsch die Konigin von Saba Uniform Title: Konigin von Saba. Festlicher Einzugs-Marsch Publisher information: Cincinnati: John Church & Co., undated (Box 158, Folder 2510)
  - Composer: Goldmark, Carl Title: Fruhlingshymne Uniform Title: Fruhlingshymne Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne Plate Number: 21546, undated (Box 158, Folder 2523)
  - Composer: Goldmark, Carl Title: Fruhlingsnetz Uniform Title: Fruhlingsnetz Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 3395, undated (Box 138, Folder 1937)
  - Composer: Goldmark, Carl Title: Fruhlingsnetz Uniform Title: Fruhlingsnetz Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 9723, undated (Box 138, Folder 1938)
  - Composer: Goldmark, Carl Title: Im Fruhling. Ouverture Uniform Title: Im Fruhling. Ouverture Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne Plate Number: 24791, undated (Box 20, Folder 224)
  - Composer: Goldmark, Carl Title: Landliche Hochzeit. Brautlied Uniform Title: Landliche Hochzeit. Brautlied Plate Number: 22136, undated (Box 20, Folder 223)
  - Composer: Goldmark, Carl Title: Landliche Hochzeit. Brautlied Uniform Title: Landliche Hochzeit. Bridal Song Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne Plate Number: 26263, undated (Box 20, Folder 222)
  - Composer: Goldmark, Carl Title: Sakuntala, op. 13. Ouverture Uniform Title: Sakuntala, op. 13. Ouverture Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne Plate Number: S.1002., undated (Box 21, Folder 232)
  - Composer: Goldmark, Carl Title: Sakuntala. Overture Uniform Title: Sakuntala. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 14907-101, undated (Box 21, Folder 233)
  - Composer: Gomez, A. Carlos Title: Il Guarany. Overture Uniform Title: Il Guarany. Overture; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 9821-68, undated (Box 21, Folder 234)
  - Composer: Goodman, Alfred Title: Selection from Linger, Longer, Letty Uniform Title: Linger, Longer, Letty. Selection; arr. Publisher information: New York: Leo Feist, Inc., undated (Box 93, Folder 1150)
  - Composer: Goritz, O. Title: Der Suesse Papa (Dear Old Dad) Uniform Title: Suesse Papa, undated (Box 146, Folder 2076)
  - Composer: Gossler, Wilhelm Title: Schiedung Uniform Title: Schiedung Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug & Co. (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: G. H. 4526 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 170, Folder 2994)